i imperil and if upanishad a voice
that the world
life on a planet is under great the evidence of it has never been cleared of an august tartanas devastated by catastrophic lading the unprecedented monorail more than fifteen hundred people and left the inundated
economic damages exceeding trevillion us oars and we been a month a scientific study had concluded the high rainbows likely increased by time
he
in my consideration of people aberdeenshire are likely to adelantamiento right maniculatus attainment willersey stone at the gesture with alessandro and unaffectionate and without
moral with the laws of god like stone power houses and the close of schools as well as rising forecasts threatening to port between five point eight and nine million people in poverty which means that according to the world banford the country is poverty radiated to rise between two point five and four percentage points as a direct consequence of the flat
the climate crises is not only imparting baltistan the overall rise in temperature has now threatened the island stonelike the maldives and bahamas awarding prisoners faces incubators would be a depth and thence for the more
now the law leaves is a country made up of almost well hundred islands scattered across ninety thousand square fomenters of also area and with it no line to ography arise and slaves good port last parts of the country under water
at the same situation stands for the bahamas with the inquiries and robertus the country is at the risk of being under water is no organstep are taken to improve the on going time
entering a new climate raillerie extreme to political and economic into
and without binding commitments or enforcement laconism avenue again and
as a way to postpone real
telling you
time
mullins
so ascelin up financing
for more on this with us of the god cases robin red aromaia its opiate director of her saturnine remain here let me begin by asking you a garasse of the way in which climate change
increasingly making its presence felt around the world
when we talk of
change and the climate change we were faced with now we're talking about and to you know climate than that resulting
from
humanity
the mission of greenhouse
globally from industrialization and other
from economic process
and this
you know the the increasingly in house as predominantly has been
senator western and developed
and
what that is resulting
changing rainfall pattern and change
and that and as a result of that
many developing countries are impacted
and you know
you know frequency
extreme weather events and
and also severity of
so is it sir
went on we mean or or what what climate change
now is all about
small small islands
in the
the benison i inly impacted and their piteous end leader
you know
standing in water or
sergeant making
it reality of the islands and they will
with
you know the
increasing what a level and
the levers and this is
even passion of aniseed
ah this recurrent like you said he this major recurrent event you know donation in africa
floods in other
you know it can change around as well there's plagiaries
so it
this happening and like i said was increased temper
you know with increased them wear and change a waterfall pattern
ability of climate and
intensity
and frequency of his
matamore and that
no governmental panelling that
and what's happening
as to livelihood life loss loss of the
you know
you know economic impacts and also
all land we are now aware a bill in your country down lord the arno get all the mules on the move
i imperil and if upanishad a voice
that the world
life on a planet is under great the evidence of it has never been cleared of an august tartanas devastated by catastrophic lading the unprecedented monorail more than fifteen hundred people and left the inundated
economic damages exceeding trevillion us oars and we been a month a scientific study had concluded the high rainbows likely increased by time
he
in my consideration of people aberdeenshire are likely to adelantamiento right maniculatus attainment willersey stone at the gesture with alessandro and unaffectionate and without
moral with the laws of god like stone power houses and the close of schools as well as rising forecasts threatening to port between five point eight and nine million people in poverty which means that according to the world banford the country is poverty radiated to rise between two point five and four percentage points as a direct consequence of the flat
the climate crises is not only imparting baltistan the overall rise in temperature has now threatened the island stonelike the maldives and bahamas awarding prisoners faces incubators would be a depth and thence for the more
now the law leaves is a country made up of almost well hundred islands scattered across ninety thousand square fomenters of also area and with it no line to ography arise and slaves good port last parts of the country under water
at the same situation stands for the bahamas with the inquiries and robertus the country is at the risk of being under water is no organstep are taken to improve the on going time
entering a new climate raillerie extreme to political and economic into
and without binding commitments or enforcement laconism avenue again and
as a way to postpone real
telling you
time
mullins
so ascelin up financing
for more on this with us of the god cases robin red aromaia its opiate director of her saturnine remain here let me begin by asking you a garasse of the way in which climate change
increasingly making its presence felt around the world
when we talk of
change and the climate change we were faced with now we're talking about and to you know climate than that resulting
from
humanity
the mission of greenhouse
globally from industrialization and other
from economic process
and this
you know the the increasingly in house as predominantly has been
senator western and developed
and
what that is resulting
changing rainfall pattern and change
and that and as a result of that
many developing
impacted
and you know
you know frequency
extreme weather events and
and also severity of
so is it sir
well we mean or what what climate he
now is all about
small small islands
in the
the benison i inly impacted and their piteous end leader
you know
standing in water or
sergeant making
it reality of the islands and they will
it
you know the
increasing what a level and
we learn this is
even passion of any
lady
ah this recurrent like
major recurrent event you know dansante continent in
floods in other
you know it can change around as well there's plagiaries
so it
this happening and like i said was increased temper
you know with increased them wear and change a waterfall pattern
nobility of climate and
intensity
and frequency of his
matamore and that
no governmental panelling that
and what's happening
as to livelihood life loss loss of the
you know
you know economic impacts and also
all land we are now aware a bill in your country down lord the arno get all the mules on the move